声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：wolfRay 螃蟹 小帝
校对：互校 时间轴：YY吕伟 leolou
========== 字幕总监制：何何  ==========
也不能说这是我们首要目的
Can't really say it's our primary objective.
那你们的首要目的是什么?
Then what is?
不好意思  我迟到了
Hello. I'm sorry I'm late.
-你一定是Burke医生吧  -我是juliet
You must be dr. burke. juliet.
Juliet
Juliet.
我叫Harper Stanhope
I'm harper stanhope.
请坐
Please sit.
我们今天只是会会面
Today is just a meet and greet
以便互相认识认识
So that we can get to know each other.
不要误解了
Please don't take this the wrong way,
我觉得我真的不需要心理治疗
But i-i really don't think I need therapy.
我们倒不如叫聊天吧?
How about we call it "talking" instead of therapy?
-那好吧  -很好
Okay. good.
聊天开始
Let's talk.
你到这儿有一周了
So you've been here a week.
到目前为止 你哪些方面不是很满意
And what's your least favorite part so far?
他们都明星一样待我
I don't like being treated like a celebrity.
很吃惊吗?
And is that surprising?
大家都在关注着你啊
You're big news right now.
对 我知道
Yes, I know.
我觉得我不想成为焦点
I guess I don't like being the center of attention.
这让我觉得很孤立
It makes me feel isolated...
孤立无援
Alone.
嗯 也许你觉得是焦点
Well, maybe you feel that all eyes are on you,
但你不算明星  很快
But you're not a celebrity, and soon enough,
你会发现你和这里的其他人没有两样
You'll realize that you're no different than anyone here.
我知道 我没有那个意思
Oh, i-i know. i-i never meant that i...
Harper  很抱歉打扰了
Harper, I'm sorry for the interruption.
我知道你不想被打断
I know you don't like me busting in,
可是Ben说他想见见这位医生
But ben would like to see the doc.
好吧  交给你了  Tom
Uh... she's all yours, tom.
很高兴跟你聊天  Juliet
It was nice talking to you, juliet.
欢迎来到这个小岛
Welcome to the island.
那是Harper的工作
That harper's a piece of work.
要是再过一周
Huckles) but if you give her a week,
她定会弄得你哭爹喊娘的
She'll have you cryin' about your dady.
这是我的个人经验
I'm speaki from personal experience here.
欢迎来到你的陋室
Welcome to your humble abode.
这是给我的?
This is for me?
整套?
The whole house?
你是来着帮我们做一些重要研究的 Juliet
You're here to help with some very important research, juliet
我们扫清了所有的障碍
We pled out all the stop
两个卧室  两个浴室  洗衣机  风干机
Two bedrooms, two baths. washer, dryer.
新窗帘  装满食物的冰箱
Fresh linens, a well-stocked fridge.
我知道你喜欢歌剧
Oh, and I know you love the opera.
所有经典的唱片都在里面
You have all the classics on cd.
Ben  真是太棒了
Ben, this is amazing.
说实在的   你本来不用这么隆重的
Seriously, you shouldn't have gone to all the trouble.
我只在这待半年
I'm only gonna be here for six months.
对  当然  但是...
Right, of course. but...
我们想让你感得自在  舒适
We want you to feel at home.
需要帮忙吗
Need some help?
我没事 只是这个好像不好固定
I'm fine. I just can't seem to get it steady.
OK
Okay.
谢谢
Nice. thanks.
何必这么麻烦呀
Why are u going to all this trouble
我们都要离开这个岛了
When we're about to leave this island?
-今晚还得有个地方打个盹啊  对吧  -Juliet
Well, I still need somewhere to sleep tonight, right? juliet.
你看见Charlotte和Faraday了吗
Have you seen charlotte and faraday?
他们的东西都不见了
All their stuff's gone.
没,卫星电话还在吧?
no, I haven't seen 'em. You still have the sat phone, right?
他看见他们往丛林中走去
He saw them going into the jungle.
他怎么不告诉我们
Why didn't he say anything?
你说过...  他们是我们的朋友
You said... they are friends.
不是吗
Aren't they?
这下够我们找了
All right, we've got a lot of ground to cer,
我们分散行动  要是发现什么蛛丝马迹
So let's fan out. if you cut their trail
就通知我  我马上过去
Call out to me. I'll come to you.
Jack?
嗨  Juliet
Hello, juliet.
好久不见
Long time no see.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我来给你传个信
I came to deliver a message...
Ben的
From ben.
你们正在找的那两个人
The two people you're looking for-
Fareday和Lewis
Faraday and lewis...
他们正在内讧
They're headed to the tempest.
如果他们发现毒气的事情
And if they figure out how to deploy that gas...
那岛上的人都得死
Then everyone on this island is going to die.
-你为什么不阻止他们  -因为Ben要你去
Why don't you stop them? because ben wants you to do it.
Ben在监狱里  怎么会知道他们的行踪
How can ben possibly know where they are when he's a prisoner?
那正是Ben想待的地方
Ben is exactly where he wants to be.
我该怎么去阻止他们
How am I supposed to stop them?
用枪指着他们  然后扣动扳机
By pointing the gun and pulling the trigger.
你是谁
Who are you?
Juliet的老朋友
I'm an old friend of juliet's.
我只是告诉她你们要找的人的行踪
I just told her where the people you're looking for are head.
要不你带上枪一起去吧
Maybe you and your gun can go, too.
你还好吧
You okay?
嗯  我正在找一些纱布
Uh, I was just lookin for some gauze.
我不知道有人在
I- i didn't know anyone was here.
怎么搞成那样?
How'd you manage that
我...
I, um...
我在那边的电站做事
I- i work over at the power station.
我碰到变压器
I was pressed up against the transformer.
坐吧
Take a seat.
让我看看
Let me take a look at it.
你是Burke  是吧
You're burke, right?
儿科医生
The baby doctor.
为什么这么说
What gave meway?
我听说Henrietta今天早上死了
I heard we lost henrietta this morning.
没关系  这不是你的错
It's okay. it's not your fault.
一个个孕妇在这里死去
Pregnant women are dying on this island.
我是来这个岛帮忙应对的
I was brought here help fix that.
那会是谁的错?
So whose fault is it?
相信我  没人期待你一夜之间就能搞定
Believe me, nobody expects you to fix it overnight.
有人陪你聊聊吗  有没有朋友也在这
You ve anyone to talk? any friends here?
可能只有Harper
Maybe harper.
Harper讨厌我
Harper hates me.
不到万不得已  我们谁都不搭理谁
We only talk because we have to.
我感觉她是个很刻薄
I get the feeling that she is a mean...
充满恶意的人
And spiteful person.
她是我妻子
She's my wife.
她是你妻子?
She's your wife?
-对不起 我不是...  -没事  不要担心
I'm sorry. I didn't- no, don't worry about it. really, it's okay. it...
好了  弄好了
Okay, you're, uh... you're set.
很感谢  女士
Much obliged, ma'am.
嘿
Hey.
我知道你很忙,如果你想找人谈谈
I know this place can wear on you, But if you need to talk...
我随叫随到
I'm around.
谢谢
Good to know.
嗯...
Oh, um...
如果你答应我不告诉你妻子
If you promise not to tell your wife
我说的话
What I said about her,
我就不告诉其他人,你的手臂的事,你撒谎了
I won't tell anyone That you lied about how you hurt your arm.
我一眼就知道是化学药品灼伤的
I know a chemical burn when I see one.
就这么说定了
You got a deal.
嗯  另外
Uh, by the way...
我叫Godwin
I'm gowin.
我叫Juliet
Juliet.
Faraday和Charlotte正在内讧
Faraday and charlotte are heading for the tempest.
我什么都不说  为了你的安全
The tempest? it's safer for you if I don't talk about it.
说说吧  拜托
No. talk about it, please.
为这个岛供电的电站
It's an electrical station that powers the island.
他们为什么要去那
Why would they go there?
你要是有什么瞒着我的话
If there's something you need to tell me,
是时候告诉我了
Now's the time to do it.
你得帮帮我
What I need is for you to help me.
你会帮我吗?
Will you help me?
如果我们整夜在赶  或许还可以追上他们
If we move all night, maybe we can still catch them.
谢谢
Thank you.
我觉得得走那边
I think it's that way.
但是要是我...
But what happens if i...
要是我失败了怎么办?
What if I can't do it?
Dan
Dan.
看着我
Look at me.
我知道你行的
I know you can do this.
我们动身吧
Should we get going?
好的
Yeah
快点
Come on.
哇  没事  没事  是Kate
Whoa, whoa, whoa. it's- it'skay. it's okay. it's Kate.
他们抓到了Miles?
So they have Miles?
是的  不过他没事
Yeah, but he's fine.
他们对他不错
They... they're treating him fine.
我还以为你们俩正和Jack在沙滩上
I thought you two are with jack at the beach.
你们在这里做什么?
What are you gs doing out here?
Jack正想和货船上的sayid和desmond通话
Jackas trying to communicate With sayid and desmond on the freighter,
但卫星电话电池耗尽了
But their sat phone ran out of juice.
死机了
It's totally dead.
我们没法和货船联系了
There's no way we can call the boat.
所以我们就自告奋勇几个
So we volunteered to get the spare batteries
去找直升机上仍下来的旅行包  里面有备用电池
Out of the packs that we threw out the chopper.
旅行包不是从飞机上仍下来了吗
So... if you threw your pack from the chopper,
这是什么?
What's that?
这个  嗯
This? uh...
这是
It's...
别人那借来的
Just borrowed is.
可以看下吗
Mind if I take a look?
随便  Dan  让她看吧
Go ahead, Dan. show her.
这是电池?
Batteries, huh?
这什么
What's this-uhh!
什么?
What?
那个女人  那个女人叫什么名字
That woman- what was her name?
Harper
Harper.
你们是朋友?
The two of you friends?
也不完全是  她是我的理疗师
Not exactly. she wamy therast.
你们配有理疗师?
You people had therapists?
干那工作  压力很大
It's very stressful.
虽说是你的理疗师  对你怀有敌意啊
Seemed kinda hostile, even for a therapist.
我相信肯定过去的有些事情
I'm sure there are things from your past
你提都不想提
That you'd rather not talk about.
是嘛  我的档案你都看到了啊
Yeah. you read them all in my file.
相信我  Jack  你一定不想看到我的档案
Trust me, Jack. you don't wanna see my file.
问题就出在
The problem occurs
在第六个月的时候
Somewhere during the second trimester,
当时母体的免疫系统正被激发
When the mother's immune system is triggered.
血液中的白细胞数量急剧下降
The white blood cell count plummets.
就好像  免疫系统对胚胎有排斥
It's like the... immune system turns on the fetus.
我可以看下吗
May i?
好的
Sure.
知道什么原因了吗
Any thought yet on a cause?
现在下定论还为时过早
Mm, it's really too early to tell, but only women
但只有在这个岛上怀孕的女人才有这种反应
Who've conceived on the island does it happen to...
-这让我很诧异  -juliet
Which makes me wonder- hey, juliet.
噢  ben  我不知道你在这
Oh, ben, I didn't know you were here.
Ethan生病了,冰箱李还有一份鸡蛋色拉
Ethan's out sick. I have an extra egg salad on rye.
-我就过来看看juliet要不要吃  -我吃过了  谢谢
I was just checking to see if juliet wants it. thanks. no, already ate.
噢 ,还有,十分钟后,我会和你妻子碰个面
Oh, besides, I have an appoinent with your wife in ten minutes.
好的  替我和她打个招呼
Great. tell her I said hi.
好的
Oh, will do.
Ben?
我没事
No, I'm fine.
那么  juliet
So, juliet,
你觉得ben这人怎么样
What do you think of ben?
相当精明
Uh, very smart...
专注
And intense.
有挑战精神
Challenging.
他一直对我很好
He's been really good to me.
那是当然啦  你好像喜欢他
Of course he has. you look just like her.
什么
I'm sorry?
我发现你和我丈夫关系很好
And I see you and my husband have become friendly.
是啊  他人不错
Yeah. he's great.
他确实很能干
He's been really helpful.
你什么时候开始和他上床的?
When did you start sleeping with him?
什么?
What?
听着  juliet  不要当我是白痴
Look, juliet, I'm not an idiot.
你就直说吧  什么时候
So just tell me. when did it start?
-我根本就没有  -我们已经分手了
Okay. I'not doing this. we're done.
你就别在耍我了
Now please respect me enough
别再装了  做都做了
To spare me the pretense that you are actually offended.
我都知道了
I know.
我跟踪你
I followed you.
监视你
Watched you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
无所谓了
It doesn't matter anymore.
现在重要的是你得听我的
But what does matter is that you listen to me
你给我记着
And that you believe me.
要是你再和goodwin
And if you continue
乱搞的话
To have a relationship with goodwin,
后果自负吧
There will be consequences.
我不想伤他的心
I don't want him to get hurt.
我永远都不愿伤害他
I would never hurt him.
我不是在说你
Look it, I am not talking about you.
我说的是ben
I am talking about ben.
嗨  john
Hi, john.
嗨  claire
Hey, claire.
能为你效劳吗
Is there something I can do for you?
我想知道你把Miles怎么了
I wanna know what's going on with miles.
现在还不好说
Right now not a whole lot.
我给他吃的喝的
I'm... bringing him food and water
直到他决定开口再决定
Until he decides to talk.
我想和他谈谈
I'd like to talk to him melf.
-为什么?  -John  我们得查出
And why would you want to do that? john, we have to find out
他们是谁  来自哪里
Who these people are and where they came from
为什么不愿救我们
And why they're not interested ine scuing us.
难度你觉得这些我都问不出来?
And you don't think I'm gonna get that out of him?
不是的  我
No, i...
我想也许我们的方法不对头
I just think we might be taking the wrong approach.
我是说  你杀了一个  ben开枪打死了一个
I mean, you killed one, ben shot one,
现在还拘捕了一个
And now we're holding one prisoner.
你知道  这样就不难理解
You know, it's not hard to understand
为什么他们认为我们是有敌意的
Why they might think we're hostile.
或许我要相对友好些
I might be just a little less intimidating.
你就死了这条心吧  claire
It's not gonna happen, claire.
-John  我不是  -你还记得charlie怎么说这些人的吗
John, I don't- you do remember what charlie said about these people.
charlie只是说
All charlie said
他们的船  不是吗
Was whose boat it isn't.
你就不想知道这些船是谁的?
Don't you wanna know whose boat it is?
今天吃兔子肉?
Rabbit today?
鸡吃完了
Running out of chickens.
上面没有编号的吧?
This didn't ve a number on it, did it?
吃吧  再把衣服换一换  完了放门边
Eat, change, put your laundry and dishes the door.
十五分钟后我来拿
I'll be back to collect them in 15 mites.
革命开始了吗?  或者叫
So has the revolution begun yet? or...
你说什么?
what are you talking about?
你是这里的头
Well, you're the leader now.
我知道这个头不好当
I know it's a tough position.
你得不断地应对人们的猜疑
You have to deal with all those people
他们总在怀疑你的决定
Constantly second-guessing your decisions,
可是他们的猜虑总是很无知  不是吗
And it always starts out so innocently, doesn't it?
问这问那   说三道四的
A question here, a comment there,
你要是一不小心
And then if you're not careful,
就肯定非得发生暴动不可
You find you have a full-blown insurrection on your hands.
相信我  你们的人一定会很愤怒
Believe me, your peopl are gonna be so angry
当他们知道你仍然没有什么计划
When they realize you still don't have a plan.
这么说你有计划了
and now you assure me that you got a plan.
我早有安排了
I always have a plan.
这和你筹集320万有关?
Does it involve you raising $3.2 million?
那可不是一笔小数目啊
Phew. that's a lot of money.
等等
Wait.
可能这个能让你开始
Maybe this'll get you started.
把你的脏衣服放到门旁边
Put your laundry and dishes by the door.
我能帮助你  John  我们的道是一样的
I can help you, John. we have shared interests...
或者  至少我们有共同的敌人
Or at least a common enemy.
你是指船上的那些人
And that would be our friends on the freighter.
不是他们  是他们的雇主
Not them. the one they work for.
把我放出去  给我点所谓的自由
Let me out of here. give me some semblance of freedom,
让我在床上睡觉  用碗吃东西
Let me sleep in a bed and eat with utensils,
我向你保证  我会告诉你想知道的
And I give you my word I'll tell you everything you wanna know
-那个派船来的人的一切事情  -但是  想想看
About the person who sent the freighter. yeah, but see,
这有个问题,我不相信你说的
There's the problem. I don't trust your word.
那好吧
All right, then.
我看我早晚都得告诉你
I guess I'll have to show you.
我希望这个味道应该不错
I hope this is good.
我不懂葡萄酒  就从潜水艇里 拿了这瓶
I don't know much about wine. I swiped this off the sub.
我真希望我们能一直这样
I wish we could do this all the time.
我很讨厌我们非得这样
I hate that we have to be so...
偷偷摸摸的
Private.
偷偷摸摸怎么了?
What's the matter with being private?
太可笑了,我在长椅上睡了一年了
So ridiculous. I've been sleeping on the couch for a year.
为什么我不能告诉她?
Why am I not just telling her?
我觉得这不是个好主意
I don't think it's a good idea.
为什么?
Why not?
Ben不喜欢这样
Ben wouldn't like it.
这是关键?  你在乎Ben的感受?
That's what this is about? you're worried about Ben?
为什么?  因为他喜欢你?
Why? because he has a crush on you?
-你知道?  -别逗了  每个人都知道
You know? come on. everyone knows.
他像宠物一样跟着你转
He follows you  like a papy.
你不觉得这有问题吗?
And you don't think that's a problem?
现在她一定在离这不足公里的地方猫着
Now a little less than a kilometer from here,
他让我负责化学品
He has me working with chemicals
如果我按错了按钮
That could kill every man, woman and child on this island
那足够杀掉这个岛上的男女老幼
If I flip the wrong switch.
相信我  Ben的权利够大了
Trust me, Ben has enough on his plate.
他根本不管你和我
The last thing he cares about is you and me.
有种感觉  他会不高兴的
get the feeling that he would be upset.
他会怎么做?
What's Ben gonna do?
Goodwin
Goodwin!
-你看见机尾降落在哪了吗?  -是的  可能在水里
You see where the tail landed? yeah, probably in the water.
你跑过去  要在一小时之内到达海岸
You run and you can get to the shore in an hour.
Ethan  你去机身那边
Ethan, get up the to that fuselage.
那里可能会有生还者  你装成一个乘客
There may actually be survivors, and u're one of 'em-
处于深深的恐惧中
A passenger. you're in shock.
如果他们问及就编个能过的去的故事
Come with an adequate story if they ask.
如果他们不问  就什么也别说
stay quiet if they don't.
听着  不要卷入其中
Listen, learn, don't get involved.
三天内我要名单  出发吧
I want the lists in three days.. go
出问题了  我们早就应该
Something's wrong. we should've...
我们早该追上他们了
We should've caught up with 'em by now.
Jack  这些人可能跳伞了
These people may be jumped out of helicopter, jack.
让他们尝尝怀疑的代价吧
Let's give 'em e benefit of the doubt.
好了好了  没事了
Hey. hey, it's okay it's okay. hey.
没事了
It's all right. it's okay. hey.
It's okay.
没事了  别担心
It's all right. come on.
慢慢来
Take it easy.
别紧张
我去弄点水
I'll go get her some water.
好的  谢谢
Yeah thanks.
发生什么了?
What happened?
我正打算回到海滩
I was going back to the beach, and...
我碰见Faraday和那个女人
I ran into faraday and that woman...
charlotte  我想是她袭击了我
Um... charlotte. I think she hit me.
他们昨晚在营地失踪了
They disappeared out of camp last night.
我们本打算追上他们
We've been trying to catch up with them.
你知道他们要去哪吗?
Do you know where they were headed?
类似于
Some sort of...
发电站之类的地方
Power station.
Jack
Jack.
他们戴着防毒面具
They had gas masks.
Juliet
Juliet?
Juliet你在哪?
Juliet!
Juliet
别玩了  别玩花样了
All right, no tricks.
你没打算把我带出丛林
You're not leading me out into the jungle
你可以消失
So you can disappear
或者在我身后放冷枪
Or shoot me in t back.
别玩花样了  John
No tricks, John.
我们甚至不用离开这房子
We don't even have to leave the living room.
那让我们开始吧
So let's have it.
我们有个交易  是吧?
We have a deal, right?
我怎么知道你会不会跑
How do I know you're not gonna run off
然后召集你的旧部?
And meet your people first chance you get?
如果我的人还需要我  John
If my people still wanted me, john,
他们早就把这营地推平了
They would've stormed this camp long ago.
在那副画后面
It's behind that picture.
密码是36, 15, 28
36, 15, 28.
"红袜队的比赛"?
"red sox"?
我把那场比赛录下来了
I taped over the game.
这是Chles Widmore
This is chles widmore.
就是他派船来的
This is the man whose boat is parked offshore.
就是他一直在寻找这个岛
This is the man that's been trying to find the island.
那个蒙着眼的人是谁?
Who's the man in the blindfold?
我的人里有一个不幸被抓到了
One of my people that had the misfortune to get caught.
-Widmore怎么知道这个岛的?  -不知道 但他就是知道
How does widmore know about the island? I don't know, but he does.
他想要什么?
What does he want?
John  三个月前在佛罗里达的Gainesville
John, three months ago in gainesville, florida,
圣母玛利亚出现在
The virgin mary seemed to appear
一个旧的居住区的附近
In a patch of mold on the side of an old housing complex.
当他说出那些话
When the word got out,
有超过5000人看到了她的脸
Over 5,000 people came to see her face for themselves.
你在空难中幸存了
You've survived an airline crash on this island.
前一分钟  你在坐在轮椅上
One minute, you're in a wheelchair.
下一分钟  你就能跳舞了
The next minute, you're doing jumping jacks.
如果有5000个人看到模具
If 5,000 people came out to see a piece of mold,
那么多少人会来这看你呢?
How many people do you think would come here to see you?
Charles Widmore想要开发这个岛
Charles widmore wants to exploit this island,
他会不息一切代价完成
And he'll do everything in his power to possess it.
我所知道关于charles widmore的所有事
Everything I know about charles widmore
都在这个文件里
Is in this file.
有些很模糊  有些全凭猜测
Some of it's vague, some of it's guesswork,
有些很具体
Some of it's concrete.
这是所有的事情  现在都归你了
But this is everything, and now it's all yours.
很抱歉  我没有早点告诉你这些
I'm sorry I did't tell you all this sooner.
但这是我唯一的筹码了
But it was the only bargaining chip I had left.
还有一件事我要知道
There's one more thing I need to know.
那个在船上的你的旧部
Your man on the boat...
我要你告诉我他是谁
I want you to tell me who it is.
好的
All right.
但是你可能想坐下
But you might want to sit down.
她从这里来
She came through here.
他们也是  大约在她前面半小时左右
So did they, about half an hour ahead of her.
发生什么了?
What happened?
对不起?
Sorry?
在locke那里  为什么你要留下?
At locke's- why did you stay?
我想找点东西
I stayed because I had to find something out.
你想告诉我,或者我们继续走,直到走出丛林
Are you gonna tell me, Or are we gonna keep walking thugh the jungle
如果不重要的话?
Like it doesn't matter?
我在那里是想知道
I stayed to find out
船上的人知不知道我是谁
If the people on the freighter know who I am,
他们是否知道我是一个逃犯
If they knew that I'm a fugitive,
一个凶杀案的嫌犯
That I'm wanted for murder.
他们知道吗?
Do they?
是的  他们知道
Yeah, they know.
我们应该继续走
We should keep moving.
鬼才知道juliet在哪
God knows where juliet is.
进来吧
Hi. come on in.
对不起  我得把这火腿从烤箱里拿出来
Sorry. I have to get this ham out of the oven,
否则它就干了
Or it'll dry out.
请你不要这么客气  你现在感觉怎么样了
Please. don't mind me. how are you feeling, by the way?
好得不能再好
Never better.
闻起来真香
It smells delicious.
Ben  我本来以为这只是个晚餐
Ben, I thought this was a dinner party.
只有我们俩
Just you and me.
我想我应该说得再清楚些
Oh,I guess I should've made that clearer.
不  挺好的  我  我希望你喜欢午餐小面包
No. it's fine. I-I hope you like dinner rolls.
我当然喜欢
I do indeed.
我想谢谢你
I wanna thank you
因为你和Zach和Emma相处得很好
For how wonderful you've been with zach and emma.
他们可都是好孩子
They're really sweet kids.
Ben,他们向我问起过,他们在洛杉矶的母亲
Ben,they've been asking me About their mother in los angeles.
我真不知道该说什么
I'not really sure what to say.
他们会及时住嘴的
They'll stop asking in time.
他们只是孩子
They're children.
真的适合呆在这儿吗?
Do they really belong here?
他们在名单上  Juliet
They're on the list,Juliet.
我们又有什么资格去问谁在名单上谁又不在?
Who are we to question who's on the list and who's not?
现在所有从尾舱来的在册人员都在这里
Now that we have everyone on the list from the tail section,
那Goodwin呢?
What about Goodwin?
这几周都不见他的踪影
He's been undercover for the weeks.
他在调查这个女人 -Anna Lucia
He's making case for this woman-Anna Lucia.
他觉得她会对我们很有价值
He thinks she'd be a valuable member of our society.
但我们私下来说  我不这么看
But between you and me,I don't see it.
他对她特别热情
He feels very passionately about her,
都有点不合适了
Almost inappropriately so.
在Ethan死后  这是在冒险
After losing ethan,it's a risk.
Goodwin正在做他该做的  Juliet
Goodwin stays where he's at right now,Juliet.
没什么原因会让他这么着急回去  对吧?
There's no reason for him to hurry back,right?
但他的任务马上就要完成了
But his assignment will be over soon.
我答应你
I promise you.
警告
Warning.
电脑转为人工控制
Computer switching to manual operation.
此次尝试未经许可
This attempt is unauthorized.
警告  系统已拒绝
Warning-manual entry
手动强制进入
Override denied.
警告  系统已拒绝手动强制进入
Warning- manual entry override denied.
反复尝试进入储藏罐
Repeated attempts to access storage tanks
将导致毒气外泄
Will result in contamination.
反复尝试进入储藏罐...
Repeated attempts to access store tanks...
嘿
Hey.
将导致毒气外泄
Will result in contamination.
Juliet
Juliet.
你来这干嘛?
What are you doing here?
最终警告  手动强制开启失败
Final warning- manual override failed.
请离开电脑
Step away from the computer.
对不起  我不能那么做
I'm so sorry. I can't do that.
手动强制开启失败
Manual override failed.
紧急对策即将启动
Countermeasures will begin.
嘿!
Hey!
毒气将在一分钟后开始释放
One minute to contamination.
你想放出毒气? 你会象我们一样死?
You wanna release the gas? You'll die with the rest of us.
不  不  不  我  我不是想放出
No,no,no. i-i'm not trying to release them.
我在试着  试着让毒气留在里面
I'm trying to-i'm trying to render it inert.
Juliet  我只想让它安全
Juliet,I just wanna make it safe.
40秒后毒气泄漏
40 Seconds to contamination.
30秒后毒气泄漏
30 seconds to contamination.
警告
Warning-
毒气即刻泄漏  赶快撤离
Contamination imminent. Evacuate immediately.
20秒后毒气泄漏
20 seconds to contamination.
不论他在做什么  让他停下
Whatever he's doing,tell him to stop.
我们试图阻止它泄漏 以免威胁到我们!
We're trying to disable it before he can use it against us!
Juliet...
看着我的眼睛  告诉我你确定
Look me in the eye and tell me you are certain
Benjamin Linus不会用这些气体
At benjan linus wouldn't use this gas
杀死岛上所有的人!
To kill evyone on this island!
我们知道他以前这么干过
We know he's used it before.
如果你想阻止我们  你就得打死我们两个
If you wanna stop us,you're gonna have to shoot us both.
10秒后泄漏
10 seconds to contamination.
-Daniel  -知道了  我在试
Daniel yeah,yeah! I'm trying.
快
Come on.
快！
Come on!
5...
4...
3...
2...
已经...
That...
已经关上了
That was a close one.
你在看什么?
What are you reading?
Shephard的资料
Shephard's fe.
Mikhail把它留下了
Mikhail dropped it off.
他是个脊髓外科医生  Ben
He's a spinal surgeon,Ben.
她在移除肿瘤方面很有经验
He has extensive experience in tumor removal.
那又怎么样?
Hmm. how about that?
他能帮你
He can help you.
我原以为你会更兴奋
I thought you'd be more excited.
怎么啦?
What's wrong?
我想让你跟我来
I need you to come with me.
我们最后一次偷袭尾舱幸存者后,他们逃离了海滩
After our last raid on the tail section survivors, They ran off,left the beach.
我派Picke和Tom跟踪他们,他们来到了这里
I sent Picke and Tom to track their location, And they came across this.
我很抱歉  Juliet
I'm sorry,Juliet.
为什么要道歉?
Sorry about what?
哦  我的天
Oh,my god.
我的上帝!  上帝!
Oh,my god! ohmy god!
哦  我的天
Oh,my god.
Goodwin
Goodwin.
发生了什么?
What happened?
我们不得而知  没有目击者
We don't know. There weren't any witnesses.
我只能猜测他们发现了他是奸细
I can only assume they found out he wasn't one of them.
我当时应该听你的
Guess I should've listened to you.
干嘛给我看这些?
Why are you showing me this?
为什么把我带到这儿?
Why did you bring me out here?
怎么  你觉得他老婆应该来?
What,you mean instead of his wife?
你知道可能的后果
You knew this would happen.
你派他来是因为你知道可能的后果
You sent him out here because you knew this would happen.
你是故意安排的!
You wanted this!
你想让他死!
You wanted him to die!
为什么?
Why?
"why"?
你问我为什么?
You're asking me why?
为了把你带来  我做了那么多
After everything I did to get you here,
为了把你留在这儿  我做了那么多
After everything I've done to keep you here,
你怎么会还不明白...
How can you possibly not understand...
你是我的?
That you're mine?
你有足够的时间
Take as much time as you need.
Kate  放松  他们在我们一边
Whoa,kate,it's all right. they're on our side.
在我们这边  Juliet?
Our side,juliet?
她刚刚把我打晕
She just knocked me unconscious.
没错  我很抱歉  但我别无选择
Yeah. I'm very sorry about that,but I had no choice.
听着  Daniel正在里面修设备
Look,Daniel's inside securing the facility
如果你们能跟我来  我将十分高兴
If you come with me,I will be more than happy
告诉你们我们是怎么救了你们一命的
To explain exactly how we just saved your life.
好吧  我们走
All right. let's go.
我相信她
I'll take their word for it.
你还好吧?
You okay?
他想让我杀了他们
He wanted me to kill them.
他命令我杀了他们俩
He told me to kill both of them.
他怎么能命令你?
How can he tell you anything?
我不知道  但他知道怎么找到我
I don't know,but he knew how to get to me,
也知道他们会去哪  会做什么
And he knew where they were going and what they were doing.
明白吗?　这些人来这
Don't you understand? these people came here
是为了和Ben开战
To wage war against ben,
而且Ben会赢  Jack
And ben'gonna win,Jack.
当他赢了  你不会想和我有任何瓜葛
And when he does,you don't want to be anywhere near me
为什么?
Why not?
因为他认为我是他的
Because he thinks that I'm his.
而且他知道我对你的感情
And he knows how I feel about you
他知道怎么找到我
He knows where to find me.
喔！
Oh!
你来打
Beat that.
婊子养的!
Son of a bitch!
你他妈的怎么会对扔马蹄铁这么在行?
How'd you get so damn good at horseshoes?
我不知道  我想我走好运了吧
I don't know. guess i'm just... lucky.
你来这干嘛?
What the hell are you doing out?
晚饭见
See you guys at dinner.
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示 |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国) 双语字幕校正 时间轴调整
英语翻译 欧美影视新闻翻译 影视评论 论坛版主 美工人员
服务器提供者 发布宣传 联系地址：www.YYeTs.net
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====